[Alice] Good morning everyone. Let's start our daily standup.
[Alice] Bob, would you like to kick us off with your update?
[Bob] Sure. Yesterday I finished the API authentication module. Today I'll work on the database migration scripts. No blockers for me.
[Alice] Great progress on the auth module. Charlie, you're up next.
[Charlie] Yesterday I completed the login form UI. I'm waiting on Bob's API to test the integration. Today I need to implement the password reset flow.
[Bob] The authentication endpoints are ready. I'll send you the Swagger documentation after this meeting.
[Charlie] Perfect, that will unblock me. Thanks Bob.
[Alice] Diana, how is the test planning going?
[Diana] I've drafted the test cases for the authentication flow. I need to review them with the team. Can we schedule a test case review session this week?
[Alice] Good question. Let's go with Thursday afternoon for the review. Does that work for everyone?
[Bob] Thursday works for me.
[Charlie] I'm free Thursday afternoon.
[Diana] Perfect. I'll send out the calendar invite.
[Alice] Before we wrap up, we need to discuss the deployment timeline. The stakeholders are asking about the release date.
[Bob] Based on current progress, I think we can have the backend ready by next Friday. The migration will need a weekend window though.
[Charlie] The frontend should be ready by Wednesday if the API integration goes smoothly today.
[Diana] I'll need at least three days for regression testing after integration. So if integration completes Wednesday, I can finish testing by Monday.
[Alice] So we're looking at a Monday release. We decided to target Monday the 15th for production deployment.
[Bob] Sounds good. I will prepare the rollback scripts as a safety measure. That's assigned to me for tomorrow.
[Alice] Excellent. Charlie, can you work with Diana to create a smoke test checklist for the deployment?
[Charlie] Will do. Diana, let's sync after this meeting.
[Diana] Agreed. I'll block some time on our calendars.
[Alice] One more thing. How do we want to handle the feature flag for the new authentication? Should we do a gradual rollout?
[Bob] I recommend a phased approach. We can start with internal users, then expand to 10% of production traffic.
[Diana] That aligns with our testing strategy. We agreed to use the phased rollout approach.
[Alice] Perfect. I'll update the release plan document with these decisions.
[Charlie] Quick question - what about the legacy login endpoint? Are we deprecating it immediately?
[Bob] We should keep it running in parallel for at least two weeks. I need to add deprecation warnings to the API response headers.
[Alice] Good thinking. Add that to your task list, Bob.
[Bob] Already on it. I'll create the ticket after this meeting.
[Alice] Alright team, great discussion. Let's recap the action items.
[Alice] Bob will send API documentation to Charlie, prepare rollback scripts, and add deprecation warnings to the legacy endpoint.
[Alice] Charlie will implement password reset and work with Diana on the smoke test checklist.
[Alice] Diana will send the test review invite for Thursday and complete the test case documentation.
[Alice] And I'll update the release plan with our decisions. Any questions?
[Bob] All clear from my side.
[Charlie] Good to go.
[Diana] No questions here.
[Alice] Great work everyone. Let's have a productive day. Meeting adjourned.